http://www.phoenixsymphony.org/pages/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Web site is the property of The Phoenix Symphony. © 2018. All Rights Reserved.
Our postal address is: One North First Street, Suite 200, Phoenix, AZ 85004
We can be reached via e-mail at info@phoenixsymphony.org or you can reach us by telephone at 602-495-1999.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumer’s access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, and payment information (e.g. billing address).
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site and used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address or writing to us at the above address.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by e-mailing or writing us at the above addresses.
To be removed from a shared email or mailing list, please provide us with your exact name and email or postal address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any Ad Server companies.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing or writing us at the above addresses.
Phoenix Symphony uses Google Analytics software. We will not (and will not allow any third party to) use the Service to track or collect personally identifiable information of Internet users, nor will we (or will we allow any third party to) associate any data gathered from our website with any personally identifying information from any source as part of Phoenix Symphony's use of the Service.
With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
Get News & Updates
The Phoenix Symphony is committed to the safety and well-being of our patrons. Click here for information about our 2020/21 Season cancellations at Symphony Hall and please click here for FAQs.
Follow Us on Twitter
Friend Us on Facebook
YouTube
©2020 Phoenix Symphony. Official Phoenix Symphony Website. The Phoenix Symphony is a non-profit 501(c)(3) organization, Tax ID 86-6000134. Privacy Policy
